DANIEL GROSSBERG

Web Developer

Harrisburg, PA 17113 717-943-4296 dwgrossberg@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com/in/dgrossberg GitHub: https://github.com/dwgrossberg

Self-motivated and meticulous problem-solver, with 2+ years of full stack web development experience. Proficient in both procedural and object-oriented programming, with excellent organizational and creative thinking skills. Strong math fundamentals (including Multivariable Calculus in college) and research background (former Fulbright Research scholar). I am a quick learner who enjoys working on difficult puzzles, both literary and logical.

Technical Skills

React.js



Professional Experience

Brand Consultant

Jan 2020 - July 2022

Five Spice Freelance, Bangkok, Thailand

- Founded a freelance branding, digital marketing, and design agency
- Expanded customer base by over 200% during our first 2 years

Senior Brand Strategist

Oct 2018 - Sept 2019

Brand Strategist

May 2016 - Sept 2018

QUO Global, Bangkok, Thailand

Managed cross-team projects involving all aspects of brand planning, such as quantitative & qualitative market research, naming, copywriting and logo design

- Created 3 innovative global brand guidelines and 25+ signature programs for Accor and IHG, including portfolio management for luxury and budget brands
- Experience leveraging B2B SaaS, CRM platforms, and innovative IT solutions
- Led 15+ client site visits, including C-suite meetings and training workshops

Marketing & PR Consultant Marketing & PR Asst. Consultant Nov 2015 - April 2016

Aug 2014 - Oct 2015

Hours worked: 80+

2019

Kenan Foundation Asia, Bangkok, Thailand

- Led the marketing campaign launch for Chevron Enjoy Science, a \$30 million, 5-year public-private project focused on improving STEM education in Thailand
- Grew social media presence by over 230% (Facebook, LinkedIn & newsletters)
- Co-wrote 2 successful USAID contract bids and designed yearly annual reports

Projects

Battleship App

JavaScript, Sass, Webpack, Jest, ESLint, Prettier

Built a test-driven development implementation of the classic game Battleship

All unit testing handling by Jest; complied using Webpack and Babel

Intuitive and user-friendly design - randomly place all of your ships with the click of a button or simply drag and drop them onto the board

Hours worked: 60+ To-Do App

JavaScript, CSS, Webpack, ESLint, Prettier, JSON

- Developed a full-scale to-do app that is functional, simple and customizable
- Leveraged OO principles, using ES-6 modules to write loosely-coupled code that adheres to the single-responsibility principle
- Wrote a module to get and set HTML's localStorage API for user-generated tasks

Hours worked: 40+ Weather App

JavaScript, CSS, Webpack, ESLint, Prettier

- Built using Async/Await, JS Promises and the OpenWeather API
- Implements JS's built-in Geolocation API to display local weather on page-load

Education

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) cum laude in English 2006 - 2010 Tulane University, New Orleans

The Odin Project 2020 - present

An open source web development curriculum

Automate the Boring Stuff with Python

Learn to automate tasks with small python programs

2012

Fulbright Research Scholar

Sichuan University, Chengdu, China

High School 2001 - 2005

Simsbury High School, Simsbury, CT